let betTxt = [
    {
        question: "slurp",
        answer: "eat or drink (something) with a loud sloppy sucking noise.\
        She was slurping the soup like there is no tomorrow. ",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "They maybe die of freezing.",
        answer: "They would have been frozen to death.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "The great wall are very long.",
        answer: "The great wall is very long.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Kuwait",
        answer: "koo-weyt",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "arab",
        answer: "ar-uhb",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "pet peeves",
        answer: "something that annoys or bothers a person very much.\
        One of my biggest pet peeves is people driving too slowly on the highway.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "That something about trouble.",
        answer: "That is troublesome.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Sometimes I get annoying.",
        answer: "Sometimes I get annoyed.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "mow the lawn",
        answer: "Arab-Christian born in Kuwait but raised in theUnited States",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "guitar",
        answer: "gi-tahr",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "contented",
        answer: "kuhn-ten-tid",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "take after someone",
        answer: "to be similar to an older member of your family in appearance or character. She takes after me with her love of horses.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "My daughter look like to me.",
        answer: "My daughter looks like me.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "I can play a few of songs with piano.",
        answer: "I can play a few songs on the piano.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "musically inclined",
        answer: "if he or she possesses a so-called natural talent for music.\
        BIBI and IU are both musically inclined ",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "I like the sound make by the piano.",
        answer: "I like the sound the piano makes.",
    }
    ,    
    {
        question: "I am quite fascinating by the sound of the piano.",
        answer: "I am quite fascinated by the sound of the piano.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "misconception",
        answer: "mis-kuhn-sep-shuhn",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "monsoon",
        answer: "the season of heavy rain during the summer in hot Asian countries. The monsoon rains started early this year.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Let me try to search on internet.",
        answer: "Let me try to search on the internet.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "He used to be live in Hong Kong.",
        answer: "He used to live in Hong Kong.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "prehistoric",
        answer: "pree-hi-stawr-ik.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "hygienic",
        answer: "hahy-jee-en-ik",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "forefather",
        answer: "an ancestor ; someone's relative who lived a long time ago. The house was built by his forefather William a hundred years before.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "I have to do anything by manually.",
        answer: "I have to do anything manually.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Most of Chinese are Han race.",
        answer: "Most Chinese are Han race.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "They look like very strange.",
        answer: "They look very strange.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "waive",
        answer: "They said they are goinig to waive all the fees for this year.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Something which annoy you so much.",
        answer: "Something that annoys you so much.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "They just look at you don't talk.",
        answer: "They just look at you and don't talk.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "divorce",
        answer: "dih-vawrs",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "widow",
        answer: "wid-oh",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Scrutiny",
        answer: "careful and complete examination.\
        One of the disadvantages of being famous is that you will always be under scrutiny.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "I don't want to be gazed by others",
        answer: "I don't like to be stared at by other people",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "His youngest daughter transferred all the money to somewhere else.",
        answer: "His youngest daughter transferred all of the money from the joint account to another location.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "calculating",
        answer: "thinking carefully about how to get exactly what you want, often without caring about anyone else. He married a calculating woman.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "period",
        answer: "a rather large interval of time that is meaningful in the life of a person, in history, etc., because of its particular characteristics\
        For example: I think Sung Dynasty is the most interesting period of history.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "I practice driving.",
        answer: "I practiced driving today.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "If I'm the person who live in the prehistoric times.",
        answer: "If I were a person who lived in the prehistoric times.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "After the Mongolia dynasty...",
        answer: "After the Mongolian dynasty...",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "Sung Dynasty.",
        answer: "I think Sung Dynasty is the most interesting period of history.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "The sound is a little bit distort.",
        answer: "The sound is a littlebit distorted.",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "condiment",
        answer: "something (such as salt,mustard, or ketchup) that isadded to food to give itmore flavor",
    }
    ,
    {
        question: "I was used to eat something goes well with ketchup.",
        answer: "I was used to eating food that goes well with ketchup.",
    }
    ,
];